RESUME

Name : - Anurag Anand Deshmukh Mobile: - +917020040535

Email ID: - nrgdeshmukh@gmail.com +919850149800

Objective

To work at a level where I am responsible for fulfilling the needs of the organization to meet its objectives and to use my skills in the best possible way for achieving the goals of the organization.

Personal information

Name : Anurag Anand Deshmukh

Date of Birth : 9th April 1992

Gender : Male

Current Address: Fat no - A-504 bhalchndra upvan, nb bhondve group, punawale,

Punawale, Pimpri-Chinchwad, Maharashtra 411033.

Educational Qualification

BE Mechanical Engineering (2016) from PCCOE, Pune, Pune with 60.7%.

Career Summary

- 7.7 years of experience in Automotive Interior.
- Basic knowledge in Plastic Interior trims.
- Ability to design from scratch and create 3D models.
- Excellent problem solving skills with strong technical background.

Organizational Experience: 7.7 years

Current Employer: IDIADA Automotive Technology India Pvt. Ltd.

Applus IDIADA Group, Unit No 304, B Wing, 3rd Floor,

Sai Radhe Building,100-101,Raja Bahadur Mil Road, Pune-411001

Role : Sr. Project Engineering- II

Working since 10 Jully 2023 till date.

Previous Employer 1: Learlauf design and engineers

No 807, City Avenue, Bengaluru - Mumbai Hwy, Wakad,

Pimpri-Chinchwad, Maharashtra 411057

Role : Design Engineer in Grupo Antolin (CAD) pune

working since 8 Oct 2016 to 14 Dec 2020.

Previous employer 2: Sphinx Worldbiz Ltd.

Role : Sr. Design Engineer in Design Engineer in

Hero motocorp, CIT, Jaipur, Rajastan

working since 15 dec 2020 to 18 Nov 2021.

Previous Employer 3: Learlauf design and engineers

No 807, City Avenue, Bengaluru - Mumbai Hwy, Wakad,

Pimpri-Chinchwad, Maharashtra 411057

Role : 1) Sr. Design Engineer in MAGNA.

Working since 21 Nov 2021 to 10 April 2022.

2) Sr. Design Engineer in Allygram.

Working since 10 April 2021 to 9 July 2023.

Technical Skill Set

- Knowledge of CATIAV5. TEAMCENTER.SMART TEAM.
- Experience of working in OEM two wheeler and tire1 automobile supplier company.
- Design and development of automotive interior plastic Trim. Including core back parts, covered parts. Removable cad methodology.
- Good knowledge of Plastic Materials, Injection Molding Process, core back injection molding process.
- Good knowledge of assembly features design like Locators, Snap, Clip tower, Doghouse, dog legs fasteners, welding bosses and ribs from library by considering RPS system with 3-2-1 principle of locating.
- Skills to design mounting concept and have experience of assembling and modifying parts according to test results.
- Checking part in DMU Analysis as well as check gap, flush, clash with environment part. Also experience of working with different department such as prototyping, vehicle integration, styling etc.
- Basic Knowledge of GD&T. Knowledge of engineering drawing for plastic parts.

Projects:

- 1) Renault HHN Kadjar EU 21 Door panel.
- 2) VW483 Door Panel.
- 3) Audi Q2 door panel.
- 4) Front and rear Bumper Ford Bronco.
- 5) Driver seat project.
 - -Bellow parts, armrest (removable cad method), and side cover parts.
- 6) Two wheeler and electric scooter plastic parts.
 - -inner panel, front cowl, side cover, seat of two wheeler, rear cowl windshield.
- 7) TATA serria IP

Rispocibility-Glovebox, Central lower panel, Hush panel LH and RH

Roles & Responsibility:

For automotive supplier company-

- Making basic close volume of parts according to section and compressions.
- Few parts according to core back manufacturing process from Renault project.
- Packaging study and creation according to bench marks.
- Create features like welding cylinder, Snap, dog house, clip tower etc
- Analyzing tooling and manufacturing feasibility.
- RFQ,Strack analysis, gap and flush analysis, ECR 21 Head impact analysis.
- Elimination of Plastic defects like sink mark, burn mark, wrap age.
- Creation of Parting line and directions for Slider, Lifter & Main tool.
- Study and design of Dynamic parts of Glove box according to functions and specifications.
- Design and development of various parts in Instrument panel.

For two wheeler project-

 Creating mounting concept, design plastic parts, and work on parts with interdisciplinary approach with VI, styling, testing departments. Creating drawings for plastic parts.

Declaration:

I consider myself familiar with mechanical design and analysis aspects. I am also confident of my ability to work in a team at any place. I hereby confirm that the above details furnished are true to my knowledge.

Place: PUNE	Yours Sincerely
Date:	A Da al
	Anurag Deshmukh